Sean Grant

Phone: 303-506-6255 | Email: Seanetella@gmail.com | Denver, CO,

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/sean-m-grant/ Portfolio: https://bit.ly/SeanMGrantPortfolio |

GitHub: https://github.com/seanmgrant

Full stack web developer with a passion for visually appealing and intuitive designs that enhance user experience. Earned a certificate in Full Stack Web Development from the University of Denver Coding Boot Camp. Creative problem-solver with an understanding of Agile development methodologies and the ability to thrive in a team environment.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

JavaScript ES6+, CSS3, HTML5, SQL, NoSQL, GraphQL, GitHub, MySQL, Express, React, Node, AJAX, JSON, iQuery, Bootstrap, Sequelize, MongoDB, Pro Tools, Logic Pro, Ableton, Premiere Pro

PROJECTS

Rush Truck Leasing | https://bit.ly/githubrushtruck | https://bit.ly/deployedrushtruck

- Summary: Information & parts database that allows a user to login and search truck models for part details.
- Role: Front End, Handlebars, and Github
- Tools: Node.js, Express.js, Handlebars.js, JavaScript, MySQL, Sequelize, CSS, Axios, RESTful API, Heroku

Rainbow Chaser | https://bit.ly/GitHubRainbowChaser | https://bit.ly/DeployedRainbowApp

- Summary: Allows users to track rainbows in their area and pin them to a map with a custom playlist.
- Role: Front End, API, and GitHub
- Tools: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Mapbox API, Genius API, GoogleFonts

Employee Tracker | https://bit.ly/GitHubEmployeeSOL | https://bit.ly/VideoEmployeeSOL

- Summary: This employee tracker is a command-line application used for managing a company's employee database.
- Role: Sole author
- Tools: Express, MySQL, JavaScript, Node.js, Inquirer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Traveling Notary/Mortgage Loan Closer Independent Consulting

(2012-Present) Denver, CO

Summary:Freelance mobile notary, traveling to homes and offices to present and notarize loan documents. Use clear and concise verbal and written communication with borrowers and show flexibility in scheduling.

- Organize and verify closing documents.
- Collaborate with title and escrow companies to ensure accuracy.
- Coordinate and schedule closings.

Founder and Owner (2017-2020)
Third and James Denver, CO

Summary: Constructed a world-class recording studio, building and maintaining both gear and clientele. Honed problem-solving and management skills. Utilized a combination of passion, motivation, and communication.

- Oversaw all marketing efforts, posting on social media and hosting events.
- Managed all aspects of operations, from running recording sessions with clients to bookkeeping.
- Headed a team of 20 employees and interns.

Stage Manager, Recording Engineer, and Sound Technician Freelance

(2011-2019) Denver, CO

Summary: Freelance audio engineer handling all aspects of a performance or event, including planning, execution, and liaising between performers, staff, and patrons.

- Implemented proper stage set-up for all performances.
- Planned and executed events for clients.
- Mixed and recorded client music, delivering high-quality audio.

EDUCATION

Certificate in Full Stack Web Development

University of Denver, CO

Associate of Arts: Audio Engineering

Musician's Institute Hollywood, CA